Guide to the International Graffiti Times archive, 1970-2000.
International Graffiti Times archive
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
International Graffiti Times archive, 1970-2000.
8067
Schmidlapp, David.
15 cubic feet.
Printed material, manuscripts, photographs, publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes 44 original, hand-collaged past-up boards from which the IGTimes page layouts were reproduced; hundreds of original manuscript, typescript, and desktop printing documents comprising the text files from which its editorial content was drawn; more than 4000 original photographs of aerosol street art submitted to the magazine by a community of international aerosol writers and readers; ca. 5000 original reader submissions; ca. 500 original magazines and fanzines; 150 clippings from newspapers and magazines; the archive of the Aerosol Art Armada, which includes ca. 1,000 35 mm. slide transparencies; a selection of flyers for parties and openings in New York City; 5 file folders with information from scholarly researchers who contacted the IGTimes for information on street art.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
In late 1983, downtown artist and photographer David Schmidlapp published the first issue of the IGTimes under the name "Yanqui Junkie." The International Graffiti Times was "the original inner-city, international, aerosol 'zine,' and the Aerosol Art Armada traveling show, providing a view of the development of aerosol street art and the rise of hip hop culture in New York City and around the world from the 1970s to the 1990s.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes 44 original, hand-collaged past-up boards from which the IGTimes page layouts were reproduced; hundreds of original manuscript, typescript, and desktop printing documents comprising the text files from which its editorial content was drawn; more than 4000 original photographs of aerosol street art submitted to the magazine by a community of international aerosol writers and readers; ca. 5000 original reader submissions; ca. 500 original magazines and fanzines; 150 clippings from newspapers and magazines; the archive of the Aerosol Art Armada, which includes ca. 1,000 35 mm. slide transparencies; a selection of flyers for parties and openings in New York City; 5 file folders with information from scholarly researchers who contacted the IGTimes for information on street art.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Schmidlapp, David.; Phase2.
Subjects:
Graffiti.; Street art.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Magazines and Fanzines
Series II. Aerosol Art Armada
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Magazine and Newspaper Clippings
Series V. Editorial Copy Files
Series VI. Flyers
Series VI. Flyers
Series VII. Correspondence
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Magazines and Fanzines
  - 14K, 1988 - 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    No. 1, 2, 5, 8-10, 13
  - 14K, 1990 - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    No. 14, 20/21, 22/23, 24/25, 46, 51, 54
  - 14K, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    No. 1-5
  - 14K, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    No. 6, 7, 9
  - 33 C Fresh, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    No. 2, 3
  - 400 Me, 1993 - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Aelle, 1993 - 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    No. 9-11, 17, 27, 29
  - Aerosol, January 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    No. 25
  - Alarm, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    No. 8
  - Allston Beat, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    2 issues, unnumbered
  - Amoeba Man, July 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Promo issue
  - AMS, undated "> (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Animals' Agenda, September 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Vol. VII No.7
  - The Anti-Draft, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Vol. 3, No. 2
  - Anti-Vigil-Anti, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Authoritarian News Network, January 1, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    No. 20
  - Apocalypso, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    No. 1
  - The Artful Dodger, February 1995 - March 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ArtPolice, January 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Two copies
  - Arts Magazine, December 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Vol. 61 No. 4
  - A.P.P.L.E., undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Backjump, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Special (two copies)
  - Backjump, 1995 - 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    No. 6-8
  - Bambina Precoce, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    No. 1-5, 12
  - Bang!, 1993 - 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    No. 4-6
  - Barcelona Game Over Magazine, 1993 - 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    No. 4, 6
  - Barcelona Zulu, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Berlin-New York, May 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Beware, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    No. 5-9, 15, 17, 19, 20, and many unnumbered
  - Biff, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Edited Highlights
  - Big Time, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Vol. 1 No. 4
  - Black Renaissance Noire, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Vol. 6 No. 1
  - Blaze, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    No. 3
  - Blacklist, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Blast, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Vol. 1 No. 4-6
  - The Blot, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bomb Hip Hop Magazine, The, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    No. 26-27
  - Bomb the Suburbs, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bomber, 1989 - 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    No. 0, 1, 16
  - Born in the Streets Graffiti, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bound Together Newsletter, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    No. 6 (three copies)
  - Brouhaha, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    No. 1-8
  - Bulldozer, 1983 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Calligraphy Review, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Vol. 11 No. 1
  - Can Control, 1993 - 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    3, 5, and three unnumbered
  - Cancer is Your Best Friend, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Capital Dread, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Captain Graffiti, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Guilt, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Centre International de Recherches Sur l'anarchisme, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Bulletin 40
  - Circle A in Atlanta, 1984 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    No. 11-13, two unnumbered
  - Circular, August 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Citizen's Law, The, May-October, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    No.
  - Clean Train, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Clout, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Issue Mot
  - Committee to Protect Journalists, 1985 - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    No. 16-20, 23-24, 27, 34-35, 41
  - Condon Man, March 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    No. 6
  - Crazy Kings Magazine, 1994 - 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    No. 3, 4
  - Crusted Dibbs, August 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Vol. 1, No. 1
  - Cultural Correspondence, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    No. 1, No. 4 undated
  - Da Juice, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Daily Battle, The, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Dance Flo Proz: A Coloring Book 4 B-Kids, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Dialogue, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Whole no. 60, 63, 64, 68
  - Duplex Planet, The, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    No. 78
  - Edition Aragon, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Effects, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    No. 2
  - Ego Trip, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Vol. 2, No. 1
  - Elements, 1996 - 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    May/June, August, Winter, Spring Editions
  - Extralarge, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Factsheet Five, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    No. 10, 14, 15-19
  - Factsheet Five, 1986 - 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    No. 20-22, 24, 27
  - Factsheet Five, 1988 - 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    No. 28-31
  - Fat Jam, March 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    No. 5 (three copies)
  - Femzine, December 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fine, December 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Flashbacks, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    No. 8, 10
  - Flip Side, 1984 - 1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    No. 43, 44, 48, 50
  - For Your Information, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Format, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Vol. 6, No. 2
  - Free, 1984 - 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    No. 6, 9-12, 16-20, 22
  - Free Ground, 1994 - 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Step 4, 7
  - Free Thought, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    No. 2, 1 unlabelled
  - French Connection, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Frontera News, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    No. 7
  - Gestalt, September 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Ghetto Art, 1987 - 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    No. 2, 4-6
  - Graf News, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Vol. 2, two unlabelled
  - Graf Work, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Vol. 1
  - Graffiti Rock Magazine, 1989 - 1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    No. 3, 5
  - Graphic Scenes, Xplicit Language, 1989 - 1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Vol. 2, No. 1-2; No. 1
  - Graphic Violence, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Vol. 1, No. 3
  - Graphotism, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    No. 1, 2
  - Graphotism, 1993 - 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    No. 5, 7-10
  - Green Zine, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Groove, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    No. 14
  - Guerilla, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - HardChorus, 1984 - 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    No. 1 (two copies), 2
  - Hates In Iran, The, June 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    No. 1301
  - Hip Hop Connection, November 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    No. 69
  - Hole in the Ozone, The, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Two issues
  - Home Boy, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    No. 2-4
  - Hoodwink, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hype, 1991 - 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    No. 12, 13, 15, 20
  - Hype, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hyper Max, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - I Am, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - I'd Rather Be Out Killing Communists, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - If an Agent Knocks, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Illitzratz, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Vol. 2
  - Insurrection, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - International Graffiti Times, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - It's Time for Anarchy Comics, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Jam Rag, 1986 - 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Vol. 1, No. 3, 5; Vol. 3, No. 27; Vol. 7, No. 23
  - Jeune Taupe, 1980 - 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    No. 32-35
  - Juice Foundation, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Jus Da Fakz, May 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Juxtapoz, 1995 - 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Vol. 1, No. 2; Vol. 3, No. 2
  - K News, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    No. 6, 13, 14
  - Keep It Real, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Kick It Over, 1985 - 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    No. 11-13, 15, 19, 21, 23
  - Kriminal Created Minds, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Liberation and Marxism, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Vol. 39, No. 20
  - Life and Death, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Life Sucks Die, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Lightworks, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    No. 17
  - Loompanics Unlimited, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mangled Efforts, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mass Appeal, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Masterpiece, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Maximum Rock N Roll, 1984 - 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    No. 17, No. 20, No. 22, No. 23, No. 32
  - Megazine Bulletin, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Melbournes Aerosol Magazine, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Molotov Cocktail, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Monthly…Bulletin, The, March 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    No. 39
  - My Buddy Notes, 1988 - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Vol. 2, No. 4-6; Vol. 3, No. 1-10; Vol. 4, No. 4-6
  - Myra, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    No. 5
  - New Instant, The, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - New World Rising, A, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    No. 1-6
  - New York Graf Monster, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Nicaraguan Perspectives, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    No. 9
  - Nog the Protector of the Pyramides, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Not Bored, 1984 - 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    No. 3, 5, 8, 9, 12
  - Novus, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    No. 30, 32
  - Now Skool, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - On the Go, 1989 - 1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    No. 3, 5, 8, 9, 14, 17, one unnumbered
  - Only in New York, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Orbit, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    No. 0
  - Original Skamster, The, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Phunk Philez, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    No. 2, 6
  - Pit Report, November 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    No. 31
  - Plaid Rabbit, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    No 26, 29 (two copies)
  - Poesie Ritrovate, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Pollution Control, 1984 - 1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    No. 2, 4-10
  - Post Graffiti, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Processed World, 1984 - 1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    No. 10, 14-16, 18, 19
  - Proletarian Warriors, undated "> (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Loose pages
  - Pzyko Vision, undated "> (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Rap Express, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Rap Pages, 1996 - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Vol. 5, No. 1; Vol. 6, No. 3
  - Rap Sheet, September 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    No. 21
  - Raw Vision, undated "> (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Real!, 1996 - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    No. 16, 17
  - Real State, The, 1994 - 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    No. 5-8
  - Red Flag, 1985 - 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    No. 8, 9, 19, one unnumbered
  - Represent, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    No. 4, 5
  - Rubber Fanzine, The, October 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Schmuck, undated "> (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Scratch Magazine, undated "> (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Scribble Magazine, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    No. 12
  - Shades, May 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Silent Scream, undated "> (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Sipapu, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Vol. 15, No. 2
  - Skills, 1993 - 1994 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sleepwalkers, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Sluggo, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Small Press Comics Explosion, March 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Small Press Review, April 1995 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Vol. 27, No. 4
  - Snarl, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Sol presents Metamorphics, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Sound Choice, 1985 - 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    No. 3, 9-11
  - Source, The, 1990 - 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    Vol. 3, No. 1; No. 30, 31, 36, 38, 40, 72, 78, 100
  - Source Awards, The, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Sparks, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Speak Out, 1992 - 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Sprayage, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    No. 4
  - Steel Wheels, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Stikem Up, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Stop Killer Cops, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Straight Force, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Street, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Stress, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    No. 1-3, 6, 10, 11, 18, 19,
  - Subculture, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Submerge, 1995 - 1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    No. 1, 3
  - Sucker: The Vampire, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Suds and Blood, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    No. 1 (two copies)
  - Survival Network Newsletter, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    No. 28
  - Swellsville, 1988 - 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Tabloid, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Technics World, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Teen Angels, 1983 - 1984 (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
    No. 3, 5, 6, 10, 23, 27
  - There's No Limit, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Thrasher, August 1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Vol. 11, No. 8
  - Tokion, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    No. 37
  - Toxic Gravity, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Second edition
  - Trace, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    No. 22
  - Train Book, The, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Transcendance, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Trap, 1992 - 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    No. 0.0, 1,one unnumbered
  - True Colorz, 1993 - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    No. 3, 5, 6
  - Truly Needy, 1984 - 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    No. 8-10
  - Tudo Aque Imaroupa, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Twelve Ounce Prophet, 1995 - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Vol. 1, No. 1, 2; No. 4
  - Underground Productions, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    No. 9, 10
  - Underground Sound times, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Unsound, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Urban, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Urban Art, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Urban Flava, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Vapors, 1988 - 1989 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    No. 1, 3, 4
  - Victorious Vandals, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Virus, 1989 - 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    No. 5, 12
  - War Craft, 1989 - 1989 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    No. 3-7
  - Warning, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - WDC, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    No. 9, 13
  - World to Win, A, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - World War 3 Illustrated, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Writer's Resource Guide, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - X-Men, January 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Vol. 1, No. 5
  - Xplicit Grafx, 1993 - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    No. 3-5, 9
  - Xylene, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Vol. 1, No. 1, 2
  - Zat, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Zig-Zag-Zine, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Zulu Nation, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Series II. Aerosol Art Armada
  - Cliff's photos, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - NYC, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Phase 2, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Coco 144, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Early Signatures, 1970-1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Writers NYC, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Vulcan, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Dez's photos, NYC, 1975-1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Trains, 1983-1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Dome NYC, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Subway NYC, 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - East Village NYC, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - IGT, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - NYC Mix, 1973-1993 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hawaii, 1985-1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - California, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Spon, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Europe, 1983-1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Australia, 1985-1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia, 1984-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Bay Area, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - California, 1990-1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - United Kingdom, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Unlabelled, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Aerosol Armada info, fact sheets, bio, letters, and flyers, 1986-1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - IGT letters, interviews, drafts, and press, 1989-1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Includes Rock and Roll, Bronx Museum, NY Press, John Nation, and New Museum.
  - Aerosol Armada paste-ups, Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Series III. Photographs
  Contains original photographs of aerosol street art, many submitted to the magazine by a community of international ‘aerosol’ writers and other readers, others shot by Schmidlapp and the magazine’s inner circle and a few from professional photographers documenting the various scenes.
  Many folders also contain flyers and correspondence.
  - Early Europe/England, pre-aerosol, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Europe, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8-12)
  - Visit to West Hollywood and East LA, plus Venice Beach, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Schmidlapp photo plus, Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Koch photos, IG Times, Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - NYC Trains and Walls, Undated (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
  - England- UK, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18-19)
  - Australia, Undated (Box 14, Folder 20-21)
  - Miscellaneous Europe, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Volume 10, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Volume 11, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Volume 12-13, Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Volume 14, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Volume 15, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Phase and Vulcan plus, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
  - Cali, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9-12)
  - America: Philly, Chicago, Miami, etc., Undated (Box 15, Folder 13-15)
  - Reproduced Trains, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Early Cali, 1983-1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Hardcore- Morgan Walker, Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Canvases- Events- Black and White, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Black and white trains, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - Michael Lawrence, Trains, USA, black and white, 1970-1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Black and white, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Letters with photos, Undated (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
  - Unlabelled, Undated (Box 16, Folder 11-13)
  - Unlabelled, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Letters with photos, many written by Cris Mendoza, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3-6)
- Series IV. Magazine and Newspaper Clippings
  - Clips: Outside NYC, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Xeroxes: Newsclips NYC, 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Copies of clippings, 1973-1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1984-1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    After Dark, The Albuquerque Tribune, Art and Artists, Arts and Entertainment
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1985-1992 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Beat Down, Bayou La Rose, Barricada, Beef
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Birmingham Post, Bitch, Bullet
  - Newspapers and clippings, Undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    The City Sun, Classic Films, Criminal Crimes, Dissident News
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1986-1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    El Salvador's Link, Elevated, Eye, Fallout, Fifth Estate, Flavor
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1986-1998 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Graffix, G.E.M.
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Hip Hop, Heads, It's Yours, K, Kick It Over, Kulcha
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1987-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Lifelines, L.A.C.E., LA Reader, LA Times, Metro
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1986-1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    National Crime and Graffiti Prevention News, New City, New Observer, NY Newsday, NY Press, A New World Rising, No Doubt
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1984-1997 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Open Road, Oregonian, Paper, Peoples Tribune, Philadelphia Forum
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1989-1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Revolutionary Worker
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1984-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Rap Sheet, RAW, Reader, Reality Now, Red Bass, Resident, Revolt
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1988-1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    San Francisco Bay News, San Francisco Museum of Art, Small Publisher, Scotland on Sunday
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    Scrawling Wall
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1988-1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Tox, Theftway, Vibe, Vilalge Beat, Voice, Yacata, Wax
- Series V. Editorial Copy Files
  Consists of manuscripts, typescript and desktop printing documents comprising the core of the magazine’s editorial content for each of the 15 issues, including interview transcripts and notes for articles.
  - Current IGT letters, proposals, statements, 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Volume 1: copy, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Volume 2, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Volume 3, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Volume 4, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Volume 5, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Volume 6, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Volume 7, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Volume 8, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Volume 9, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Volume 10, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Volume 11, 1986-1990 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Volume 12 and 13, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Volume 14, Undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Volume 15, Undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Unpublished, Undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - IGT xeroxes of issues/posters, 1990-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Xeroxes of press clips and covers of press, 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - IGT Promo writings: Schmidlapp, 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Flyers, letters, IGT xerox, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Rockathon entries, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rockathon entries, Phase 2, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Stickers, Undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Series VI. Flyers
  - Flyers and pamphlets, 1980-1999 (Box 20, Folder 14-16)
    Includes some business cards
  - A selection of fliers for parties, openings, and events in New York City featuring the magazine itself and members of the IGTimes community, including correspondence with alternative art spaces ABC no Rio, Fashion Moda Gallery, Franklin Furnace and Food Stamp Gallery, ca. 1984-1994., Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Flyers, art, letters, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, clippings, and sections from zines, Undated (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
    Includes Writer's Resource Guide, War Craft, New Urbanism, Café Armageddon, 14k, Bullshit Monthly
  - Artwork, Undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Flyers, "Get Hipped", Undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Flyers and artwork, Undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Series VII. Correspondence
  Consists mainly of reader submissions including letters, postcards, original artwork, photographs and other items from local and international correspondents, as well as mail art, prisoner and G.I. letters, and subscription requests
  - Letters, 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Letters, 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Letters from prisons and some military, 1987-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)